Finding aid for the Alan Mandell papers, 1950-2012 LSC.2123
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 3: Theater Companies, 1952-1995
  - Subseries 3.4: The Los Angeles Actors' Theatre (1975-1985) and The Los Angeles Theatre Center (1985-1991), 1975-1995
    Contains records relating to the management of the Los Angeles Actors' Theatre and the Los Angeles Theater Center, particular theatrical productions, and the popular Poetry/Literary Series initiated and overseen by Mandell. The poetry materials may be of special interest to scholars interested in supplementing the existing scholarship on breakthrough readings and festivals with descriptions of the role played by regular reading series in the dissemination of the art.
    - Photographic History, circa 1975 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Cast Lists (1 of 2), 1977-1990 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Cast Lists (2 of 2), 1977-1990 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Tokyo Rose Article, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Playwright's Workshop, circa 1980 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Apprentice/Intern Program, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Programs and Brochures, 1980-1989 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Photographs (1 of 2), 1980-1999 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Photographs (2 of 2), 1980-1999 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Response to Review of "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!", 1981 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Theatre Facts, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Throne of Straw, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Throne of Straw - Photographs, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Basics - Los Angeles Actors' Theatre, 1981-1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Agents-Clients List, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - V.I.P. Master List, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Play Rejections, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Press (1 of 2), 1982-1989 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Press (2 of 2), 1982-1989 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - EZTV Vietnam Screening, circa 1983 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Happiness by Mayo Simon - Script, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Happiness and Walking to Waldheim by Mayo Simon, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Quannapowitt Quartet, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Proposal for the Steve P. Jobs Performing Arts Center, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - "The Family" Project, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - These Men by Michael Imison, 1983-1985 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Performing Arts Center Materials, 1983-1986 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - A Rich Full Life by Mayo Simon (1 of 3), 1984 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - A Rich Full Life by Mayo Simon (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - A Rich Full Life by Mayo Simon (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Grand Opening, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Lannan Foundation, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Nanawatai, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Personnel Manual and Policies, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Programs, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Samuel Beckett - 3 by Beckett - Basics, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Beckett - 3 by Beckett - Company, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Beckett - 3 by Beckett - Company Photographs, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Beckett - 3 by Beckett - Footfalls Photographs, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Contact Sheet, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - The Birthday Party by Harold Pinter - Photographs (1 of 3), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - The Birthday Party by Harold Pinter (2 of 3), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - The Birthday Party by Harold Pinter (3 of 3), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - The Birthday Party by Harold Pinter - Program Notes, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - The Birthday Party by Harold Pinter - Reviews, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - The Birthday Party by Harold Pinter - Schedule and Script, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Happy Days by Samuel Beckett, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Limited Partnership, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - New Plays Development Series, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Overview, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Poetry Article - Los Angeles Reader, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Subscription Agreement, circa 1986 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Poets/Readings, 1986-1990 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - American Directors Institute, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Artistic Statement, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Bookshelf Inventory, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Festival, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - The Film Society, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - The Film Society - Photographs, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Organizational Chart, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Poet's House New York, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Six Directors in Search of an Audience Symposium, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Theatre Communications Group Inc., 1987 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Theatre As A Learning Tool Educational Project, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - What the Butler Saw, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Publishing Houses, 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Poetry Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Poetry Reading Schedules, 1987-1989 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Various, 1987-1991 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Bill Thompson/Briarwood Writer's Alliance, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Board Retreat, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Candles of Conscience, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - The Caretaker by Harold Pinter, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - The Caretaker by Harold Pinter - Photographs, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Production Fact Sheets, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - L.A. Poetry Festival, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - New Poets, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Poetry Costs, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Poetry Fact Sheet, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Poetry Series - Various, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Publications, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Script Analyses, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Spring/Summer Season 1988 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Staff, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Poetry Sales, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Actors List, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Board of Trustees, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - Poetry Series, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Finance Committee, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - National Funding, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Ruth Alben Speakers Service, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Business Plan, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - The Dance of Death (1 of 2), 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - The Dance of Death (2 of 2), 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - The Dance of Death - Photographs, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - The Dance of Death - Script, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Executive Committee, 1989-1992 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Contacts, circa 1990 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - The Illusion, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - The Illusion - Photographs by Rosemary Kaul, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Income/Expense Comparison by Gerry Horton, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Institutional Press Kit, circa 1990 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Poetry/Literary Materials, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Poetry Subscribers Mailing List, circa 1990 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Programs from Other Theaters, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - A Ward Ballad, circa 1990 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Poetry File, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Poetry Series Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Academy of American Poets, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Audit, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Brochures, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Crisis, Memo to Bradley, Clippings, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Day of Hope Contact Sheet, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Festival of New Works, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Finances, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Labs, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Mailing List, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Memos, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Pending Sale, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Production Schedule, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers Union, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - University of Southern California (USC) Playwrights Guild Fest, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Notes on Theater from Herbert Blau and Jules Irving, circa 1992 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - A Place at Forest Lawn, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - L.A. Style Article - Keeping Company with Alan Mandell (Oversized), 1985 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Company Poster (Oversized), 1986 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Series 4: Subject Files, 1950-2012
  Contains contracts, correspondence, notes, photographs, press, programs, productions schedules, and scripts related to specific theater and film productions, including the 1973 Broadway revival of A Streetcar Named Desire produced by Mandell, the 2006-2007 production of Twelve Angry Men, Hedwig and the Angry Inch (2001) and Shortbus (2006) by J.C. Mitchell, and A Serious Man (2009) by Ethan and Joel Cohen.
  - The Actors Center, 1999-2006 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - The Actors Studio, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - American Theater Series in Italy Invitation, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Angels in America Part One by Tony Kushner - Script, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Angels in America by Tony Kushner - Los Angeles Times Review, 2012 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Antaeus Company, 1996-2007 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Anvil Entertainment, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - A.S.K. Theater Projects, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - The Beard of Avon, 2003-2012 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - The Beard of Avon - New York Theatre Workshop, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Beechwood Drive, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Bergamont Station, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - The Blind Owl - Production Notes, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - The Brothers Karamazov - Taper, Too, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Cabaret Verboten, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Cal Arts Photographs, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - The Cherry Orchard - Contract, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - The Cherry Orchard - Reviews, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - The Cherry Orchard - Basics, 1995-2006 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - The Cherry Orchard - Santa Fe and Taos, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - The Cherry Orchard - Cast and Contacts, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - The Cherry Orchard - Opening Night, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - The Cherry Orchard - Photographs, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - The Cherry Orchard - Reviews, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Children's Theatre, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Classical Theater Lab, 1990-1999 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Clippings of Interest, 1984-1988 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Communications Bridge (Brock and Dioi), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Craft and Folk Art Museum (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Craft and Folk Art Museum (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Dance of Death, undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Dar a Luz Benefit, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Denial (1 of 3), 1995 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Denial (2 of 3), 1995 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Denial (3 of 3), 1996 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - A Dram of Drummhicit at La Jolla Playhouse, 2011 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - The Dream Coast, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Eleutheria, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Elvire Jouvet 40 Script by Brigitte Jacques, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - An Evening of Conversation with Rick Cluchey and Alan Mandell, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Falcon Theatre, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - The Forum, 2010 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - The Gambit, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - A Gift of Fury by Herbert Blau, circa 1960-1969 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Golf with Alan Shepard, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Gontarski Critique, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Greenlight Entertainment, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Grey's Anatomy Television Episode, 2010 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Habimah Theater, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Half Life, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Hedwig and the Angry Inch, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - The Hedwig Company, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - He Hunts, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Hip-Hop Waltz, 1990-1991 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Hip-Hop Waltz - Barcelona, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Hip-Hop Waltz - Hip Hopping Mythology by Richard Stayton, circa 1991 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Hip-Hop Waltz - Montreal, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Hip-Hop Waltz - Paris, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Hip-Hop Waltz - Script, circa 1995 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Hollywood Film Music, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Hollywood Symphony Antony and Cleopatra, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Hysteria, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - I Am A Woman by Viveca Lindfors, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Impossible Marriage by Beth Henley, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Impossible Marriage by Beth Henley - Script, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Impossible Marriage by Beth Henley - Contacts, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Impossible Marriage by Beth Henley - Fan Mail, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Impossible Marriage by Beth Henley - Photographs, 1998-2012 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - King Lear (1 of 2), 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - King Lear (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - The King's Speech by David Seidler - Script, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - L.A. Center Theatre Group, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - L.A. Stage Ovation Awards, 2011 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - L.A. Theatre Works, 2002-2010 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - L.A. Weekly - Stage Fright, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Lannan Literary Videos, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Latino Theater Company, circa 2004 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Lordly and Dame, Inc., 1986-1989 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Love's Labor's Lost, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Love's Labor's Lost at the Old Globe, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Mabou Mines, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Magic Theatre - Mame Hunt, 1996-1998 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Magic Theatre - Skylight, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Mark Taper Forum - Theatre du Soleil in The House of Atreus, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Max Headroom, circa 1987 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Merchant of Venice, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Merchant of Venice - Photographs, circa 1993 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Merchant of Venice - Reviews, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Merchant of Venice - Script, circa 1996 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - MET Theatre Los Angeles, circa 1988 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Metropolitan Opera Program, 1966-1967 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Milestone Film and Video, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - The Mission Project (Franciosa), undated (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Mizlansky/Zilinsky or "Schmucks", 1998 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Moscow, U.S.S.R., 1988 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - My Dinner with Andre, 1982-1984 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - National Poetry Month, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - National Repertory Theatre Foundation - Playwrighting Contest Notes, 1996-1997 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - New York Theatre Workshop, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - A Noise Within, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - No Man's Land by Harold Pinter at the Odyssey Theatre, 2009-2010 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Nuts for the Underman by June Havoc - Script, circa 1990 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Obediently Yours, Orson Welles by Richard France, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Oh Glorious Tintinabulation by June Havoc, circa 1990 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Old Groucho's Game by James Schevill - Script, circa 1985 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - The Old Lady's Guide to Survival - Chicago, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - The Old Lady's Guide to Survival - Contracts, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - The Old Lady's Guide to Survival - Director's Notes, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - The Old Lady's Guide to Survival - Louisville, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - The Old Lady's Guide to Survival - New York, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - The Old Lady's Guide to Survival - Receipts, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - The Old Lady's Guide to Survival - Reviews and Mail, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - The Old Lady's Guide to Survival - Selznick (1 of 2), 1993-2001 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - The Old Lady's Guide to Survival - Selznick (2 of 2), 1993-2001 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Olympic Arts Festival UCLA, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - The Orestia, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - The Orestia - The Actors' Gang, 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Pipe Night at the Players Club, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Pittsburgh Public Theater, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Playbills, 1985-1992 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Playbills - Signed, 1963-2004 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - The Players Club, 1994-1997 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Playwrights' Arena, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Providence, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - QRS Family Committees, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Restoration by Claudia Shear - Script, 2012 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Restoration - New York Theatre Workshop, 2010 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Restoration - Press, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Road to Mecca, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Road to Mecca - Photographs, circa 1989 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Road to Mecca - Tax Information 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Road to Mecca - Reviews, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Roundabout Contract and Insurance, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Royal Family (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Royal Family (2 of 2) - Opening Night Cards, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Salvation Square, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Sarcophagus, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Save Me a Place at Forest Lawn, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Scena Theater, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - A Serious Man by Ethan and Joel Cohen, 2009-2010 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Shakespeare - Conference, 1996 April (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Shakespeare - GroveShakespeare, 1991-1993 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Shakespeare - New York Shakespeare Festival, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Shakespeare - Orange County Contacts, undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Shakespeare - The Shakespeare Festival Los Angeles, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Shortbus by J.C. Mitchell, 2003-2008 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Shortbus by J.C. Mitchell - Notes, 2003-2008 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Shortbus by J.C. Mitchell - Script (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Shortbus - Script (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Siberia, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Siberia - Moscow, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Silver Queen Saloon, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Silver Queen Saloon - Budgets, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - A Slight Ache (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - A Slight Ache (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers, 1994-1998 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - "Sonya" Reading, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - South Coast Repertory - The Hiding Place, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Stage Fright - Charles Marowtiz, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - The Tempest, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - The Tempest - Research, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - The Tempest - Reviews and Criticism, circa 1998 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - The Tempest - Script, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Theater '49 Toronto, circa 1952 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Theatre at Saint Clements at Death Star, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Theatre Vanguard, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - The Trial of the Chicago 7, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Toronto Civic Theatre, circa 1957 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Trying, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Trying - Contract, 2008 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Trying - Interview, 2008 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Trying - Press, 2008 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Trying - Reviews, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Trying - Script Notes, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Twelve Angry Men, 2007-2008 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Twelve Angry Men - Letters, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Twelve Angry Men - Programs, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Twelve Angry Men - Reviews, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Twelve Angry Men - Second Run, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Twelve Angry Men - Tour, 2007 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Twelve Angry Men - U.S. Tour, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - An Unexpected Evening with June Havoc, circa 1990 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - van Praag, Judith, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - The Vanya Company, 2000 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Various Subject Files, 1990-2011 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Venture West Theatre Company, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Stage Company, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - When the World Was Green, 1996-1998 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - When the World Was Green - Contract, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - When the World Was Green - Photographs, circa 1996 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - When the World Was Green - Reviews, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - When the World Was Green - Script, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - William and Flora Hewlett Foundation, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Williamstown Theatre Festival (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Williamstown Theatre Festival (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Witch Hunt - Prosecution by Piety (on Arthur Miller's The Crucible), circa 1990 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Writers on War, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - You Never Can Tell - Budget, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - L.A. Village View Issue (Oversized), 1993 November (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - BackStage Article - Actors We Love (Oversized), 2004 June (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Series 5: Audiovisual Materials, 1980-2010
  Contains various audiovisual recordings and an audio box set of Samuel Beckett's Three Novels (2006). Includes readings by Beckett and The Impossible Itself (2010), a documentary by Jacob Adams about the San Quentin performance of Waiting for Godot.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Contains eight DVDs, an 18-CD box set of Samuel Beckett's Three Novels (2006), five additional CDs, and six audiocassettes, and two audio reels.
  SERIES CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - Adams, Jacob. The Impossible Itself. DVD., 2010 (Box 45)
  - Allaman, Eric. The Overture to Stendhal. Audiocassette., 1988 (Box 45)
  - Beckett, Samuel. Three Novels: Molloy, Malone Dies, The Unnamable. Read by Barry McGovern. RTE/Lannan: 2006. CD Box Set (18 discs). (Box 45)
  - Beckett, Samuel. 3 1/2. Bells (revised). Footfalls - Mother. Audio reel., undated (Box 45)
  - Beckett, Samuel. Rockabye. 7 1/2 P.S. Full Track Mono. Audio reel., undated (Box 45)
  - Beckett, Samuel. Mother - Footfalls. Taped during performance. Audiocassette., undated (Box 45)
  - Beckett, Samuel. Lessness. Read by Samuel Beckett. CD., undated (Box 45)
  - Beckett, Samuel. Waiting for Godot. DVD. (1 of 2) - Act I, undated (Box 45)
  - Beckett, Samuel. Waiting for Godot. DVD. (2 of 2) - Act II, undated (Box 45)
  - Beckett, Samuel. Waiting for Godot. DVD, undated (Box 45)
  - The Deluxe Vaudeville Orchestra. Deluxe Attire Encouraged. Audiocassette., circa 2005 (Box 45)
  - Dram Songs. CD., 2011 (Box 45)
  - Grey's Anatomy. "Shiny Happy People." DVD. (1 of 2), 2010 (Box 45)
  - Grey's Anatomy. "Shiny Happy People." DVD. (2 of 2), 2010 (Box 45)
  - Havoc Reading "UE" New Materials. Audiocassette., 1980 (Box 45)
  - Iacovelli, John. Designer. DVD., undated (Box 45)
  - Mandell, Alan and Rebecca. "Trying" Interview. CD., undated (Box 45)
  - [Mein Madel]. Audiocassette, undated (Box 45)
  - Mitchell, J.C. Shortbus Soundtrack. CD., 2006 (Box 45)
  - No Man's Land Photographs. DVD., 2006 (Box 45)
  - Schwartz, Craig. Photographs. CD., undated (Box 45)
  - Siberia. Audiocassette., undated (Box 45)